It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a winter fire.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'll not stay.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, baby!
No one can make it, my dream come true?
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is?
Something is testing.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the crazy.
I know that I know you.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm no afraid with me.
Hit me, I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so?
Can you only wait out?
We can let go together.
Baby, grow up with a rose.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fight it for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your wife.
That I want, but you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of days.
You make my day every day.
Niko Robin just lovely how cowardly gave
yourself the advantage I
what wait wait dear girl.
I'm a bad guy.
You expect me to fight fair?
Yeah.
Sorry, that's rich.
Time to die.
Funny.
You have it backwards.
Go on.
Commander, Rebecca's safe.
Don't hold back.
She's with me.
Thank you. Sincerely.
Long have I waited for revenge.
What are you guys up to?
Have mercy on us!
We're just respectfully
moving the corpses.
Please don't take it the wrong way. Okay.
I'm pretty sure that
one's still alive, though.
Fair, but can we agree he's
knocked out cold, right?
At least let us tend to
his wounds, pretty please.
Please, sir.
Can you show us pity?
We appeal to your honor.
Oh, please. All right.
Hit the bricks.
Thank you very much.
Sheesh.
Oh, senor.
Connected.
Ms.
Viola, you there?
Please respond
Hello?
How's the princess? Or Leo?
What a mess, our beloved princess.
How I worry for the girl!
Is she well?
I must know There's news, it's not good.
We ran into a problem.
Don't see something happen to her.
Just a moment, please.
Stay on the line while
I contact the others.
Leo, can you hear me? Oh, Ms.
Viola We're running up the
rampart tower at the moment.
So close.
We're approaching the chapel.
Do whatever you must to get there quickly.
Giola has Princess Moncherry and is
forcing her to use her ability. What?
That's really bad news.
Oh, no.
Hurry up, Leo.
It's the little people.
They're approaching.
Shoot them.
Bring in the explosives.
Take them out.
And a staircase, too!
Keep up the pace! Almost there!
Hang on, Princess Moncherie!
We're on the way!
Stop giving me a hard time, Princess.
Do as I say!
I won't anymore!
Hi, Miss Greenbit.
Could you please let me go?
I can't help you any longer.
Shut your mouth.
Who are you calling Boa Hancock?
I never said that.
You misheard me.
Don't be a baby.
Princess, please.
We need your cooperation.
Just look.
Are you really going to
let the executives suffer?
Listen, they lost to our
enemies, but not by much.
Meaning the people they fought are
in pretty rough condition themselves.
So,
if you'll work with me
here and use your heal
-heal fruit powers to
revive our executives,
we'll win!
They'll be able to finish the job and
send those louts to an early grave.
Our foes will never see it coming!
Now,
are you ready to use
that Fancy Pants ability
like you did on Sugar
the first time she lost?
Come on, hang that magic
watering can over here.
Now, now, now.
I cannot.
I know the truth.
I won't help.
You're very bad people.
You hurt King Rick.
I also found out that King
Doflamingo has been lying to us.
And that was all for your own
good, you know-nothing rat.
I don't want to heal bad guys like you.
No more.
She...
She's so cute.
So cute!
Don't fall for crocodile tears.
Did you just call me the
beauty of the millennium?
Hooray!
Help me!
Alright then.
I see how it is.
You don't care about your friend, huh?
But if I heal all your people's wounds,
they'll do bad things again, won't they?
Hush, girl.
I suppose I have no choice but to
wring the powers out of you, then.
Help me! Leo!
Hit something that time.
Cub!
Leo! Cub! Something wrong?
Fight on!
I'm fine!
Go on ahead without me!
I'll catch up!
Stop it!
It's painful!
What happened?
Oh, look, he's better.
Keeping secrets, little princess.
So even your tears have
the ability to heal people?
Cry for me!
No!
Come on, Princess!
Weep those little eyes out!
It's raining me!
Please, no more!
Leo, hurry! On it!
Speak up. What's wrong?
It's Yola!
She's figured out the
princess's dearest heal people!
She's forcing her to cry by
callously inflicting pain!
No!
I'll be right there!
Mauji's coming!
It's no use!
We can't help!
It's up to Leo and Cub!
She sounds powerful.
I get why they wanted her.
Because of the heal heal fruit.
It's granted her the ability
to mend wounds of all
living things and they're
forcing her to use it Jeez,
I see damn. Yes.
Damn now.
They're harming her It's a twisted attempt
to revitalize their defeated executives.
It'll be bad if they pull it off
And I thought we were
in the clear Leo, hurry!
Go Cub, quickly!
Don't tell me.
Sugar's there with them, too, isn't she?
She is.
Whaaaaat?
How the heck do we even the
odds when they keep coming back?
Come on, Leo!
Go! Go!
Run, little guy!
Save the girls!
Found it!
The naughty room!
Hey, you! Drop her!
Leo!
Princess!
You're too late, hero.
Grab her!
Now, wake up, everyone.
Time for the Don Quixote family reunion.
Round two, start!
Leo, move it!
You handle Giola. Go!
No!
Uppaca!
But how?
So, so, so, so, so!
So!
It's fine.
I'll line them up again.
You should have grabbed her.
Then let me help you with that.
So, so, so!
So, so, so, so, so!
Huh?
I strung you all together.
So your friends won't
get separated anymore.
You what, Atlas fool?
Hot Couture!
Patchwork, go! Oh, no!
Leo really came to rescue me.
He's just like a real prince.
That...
was crafty.
He made it!
Just in time! He did?
It's over?
Madam Ninja!
The executives weren't revived.
Leo stopped her!
Tiny individuals!
Splendid work!
Monsherry is with Leo!
All right!
Leo, I was scared!
Yeah?
Hey, did you gain some weight?
Classic Leo.
Leo!
My leg was hurt bad.
Can you carry me on your back?
Or maybe in your arms?
There you go again,
acting like a big baby.
You can fix your own injuries.
You have healing powers, you lazy dummy.
Besides, I know you've
always been a good runner.
Stop playing games.
We've got to hurry.
Lady!
I'm staying then.
What? For real?
You're so selfish.
I never asked for you to
come here and save me, Leo.
I put my life on the line.
You are so ungrateful.
Do you really want me to leave you here?
Go!
Just carry her out for now.
We got to go.
That hurt.
You're obnoxious.
Selfish, fickle, despicable,
and mean-spirited.
Such a huge, huge pain in the patootie.
His back feels nice.
Our princess is just the sweetest.
How thick-headed can Leo be?
Big problem!
They took Mad Sherry and ran off!
Go after the little people!
They went that way!
Seize them!
How embarrassing.
I hate to admit defeat, but
the situation has become dire.
He won't be thrilled, but I
must report to the young master.
I recall him saying that Mancherry's devil
fruit must have a hidden ultimate ability.
He believed that he could use that if
something happened to the Smile Factory.
If she traded her life to call
forth that forbidden power,
she could restore it to its former glory.
Without that fail-safe,
we could be in trouble.
If nothing is done, then
the factory is in peril.
It's on you, senor.
You're our last line of defense. Franky!
No!
Senor, please be careful.
Strong hammer!
Ah!
He dove in the ground again!
Farland, look!
It's the attack dive!
Dive!
Meow meow!
Suplex!
Oh, this is Yarr!
Senor must be at his limit.
Froland!
Something's wrong.
You could have easily dodged that.
What's with you?
Why'd we see you take the
same move over and over again?
Stay out of this, tontadas.
You know, Senor's also been hit with
the same punch 30 times in a row, too.
Why would he do that?
When someone offers to
buy a round at the bar.
If you're a real man, then you wouldn't
dare take your glass off of the table!
You're getting hit on purpose?
This guy's a bro among bros.
So I'm gonna take every attack
he throws at me out of respect.
He can throw whatever he's got at me.
I'll still win
We're doing it strong style, baby
It's cute that you're concerned,
but this is a man's
fight So just stand back
and watch me win don't
fret little friends.
I won't let you lose your freedom
Your words make me tipsier than
any dive bar I'd ever been to, kid.
I'd like to see you
back up that fancy talk.
I'll confess.
This body's not as spry as it used to be,
so my next move is going to settle these.
How are you two going to fight
when you're so far apart?
Signor, closer!
Hey, pervert, are you picking
up what I'm throwing down?
You said you'd take whatever
I can hurl at you, right?
True men don't go back on their word.
So let's see you try.
Surviving this one!
If you can withstand this
final blow, I'll take the loss.
I'll accept whatever attack
you wish to dish out.
Bring it on!
He swam straight up the side of the tower!
What in the heck is that
guy gonna do up there?
That's a mean-looking sky
today, don't you think?
But if I can keep flying, then
maybe I can see my Russian,
Russian, yeah, I'd like to see my son.
Gimlet too, unfortunately, gravity
is going to fight me on this,
and I can't keep flying.
Hey, what are you rambling about?
Tell me, Cyborg, your back's
still flesh and blood, right?
Oh, damn it!
You figured that out!
Now shut up before you
bite your own tongue off!
Meow meow suplex!
Baby...
Buster!
Oh, my God.
Frawl 'n!
Remember your words, old man.
Now you'll get to see what I'm made of.
Oh, you got me there.
I'm sorry, young master.
All right, Franky Iron Foxy!
I remember now, Russian.
The day I first met you, and
the day you stopped smiling.
That cold dark rain kept
pouring, just like in my heart.
It's a wet one out there, huh?
I'm drenched.
What's so amusing?
Aren't you freezing cold?
It's fine.
I love rain.
Feels nice.
What things don't I like?
Oh, pirates hate him to
death, so what do you do?
Me? I'm a... a banker.
Oh.
There you are.
So, honey, what should we name him?
He looks like...
a Gimli.
I think that suits him fine.
Gimlet is dead.
A week ago today.
The same day you disappeared.
He came down with a sudden fever.
I rushed him to the hospital.
But he didn't make it.
You lied.
I called the bank over and over.
But they told me you were
never employed there.
Tell me the truth!
What do you really do for a living?
Where did the money come from? Say it!
Hey!
Why won't you tell me?
You don't have the right to
be a father anymore Move!
Wait!
Wait! Russian!
It's terrible out here
You stop following me!
I need to be alone now.
You don't understand, Russian.
There's a reason I can't
tell you the truth.
Russian!
Where are you?
I'm sorry to report.
Your wife is in critical condition.
She was trapped under a
landslide during the storm.
She's awake, but unresponsive.
A vegetative state?
Exactly.
The trauma has left her
with no signs of awareness.
And I'm afraid she may never recover.
Sad to say, the woman you
once knew was no longer there.
I'm not entirely sure how
much time she has left either.
If only you hadn't met me.
This would have never happened.
Honey, thanks so much.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to lose you.
That's why I lied.
I want to hear your voice.
I want to hear you laugh.
Just once more.
I want to see your smile.
Hey, Russian, look here!
I found the same bonnet that
our gimlet used to wear.
Don't I look like him?
You used to say he had my face. I'm sorry.
That was a poor joke.
And just imagine if somebody saw me...
Russian...
Oh
Aren't you a Kaido?
I heard he lost his son
and his wife's brain dead.
No wonder he went off the deep end.
What is this?
The hell happened to
your fashion sense, Pink?
I'm heading out.
Look, it's a weirdo.
Keep walking, you perv.
What a creep. Look! It's a freak!
Hey, stop that!
Russian.
I look ridiculous.
But to me, this silly outfit is
worth more than the finest suit.
The only time you smile for me
anymore is when I wear this.
Hang on, senor!
Rollins, tell us that you're okay!
You're a real mess, bro.
What's going through your head right now?
What's making you hurt like that?
Tell you what, if we ever cross
paths again, let's have a round.
You can tell me all about
that girl who goes by Russian.
You